## **Kevin Ramos**

11040 Tortuga Bnd #102, Orlando, 32825, United States, 407-923-8849, K.ramos109@yahoo.com

LINKS	Github, LinkedIn			
PROFILE	Diligent Software Developer with experience in Web Development and cross-platform mobile applications. Proficient in various platforms, languages, and embedded systems. Is self-reliant exhibited by his experience as a founder of multiple small businesses, as well as highly collaborative in a productive team.			
EDUCATION				
Aug 2019 — Dec 2021	Bachelor of Computer Science, University of Central Florida Orlando			
	<ul> <li>GPA 3.6</li> <li>Coursework: Discrete Mathematics, Object-Oriented Processes, Computer Science 1&amp;2, Data Structure &amp; Algorithms</li> </ul>			
PROJECTS				
Feb 2021 — Dec 2021	MyThirdEar			
	Designed the user interface and created the audio processing and looping mechanisms for a cross-platform mobile application that helps musicians transcribe music by ear			
	Technology used: Dart, Flutter, Android Studio			
Jan 2021 — May 2021	Pac-Man 3D			
	Implemented shadows, graphics, and a joystick mechanic for a browser-based 3D Pac-Man game			
	Technology used: TWGL, WebGL, JavaScript, and HTML/CSS			
Jan 2021 — Mar 2021	Farmers vs. Aliens!			
	Implemented the path-finding mechanism, and designed the game play and object interactions			
	Technology Used: C# and U	Jnity		
SKILLS	Python	Experienced	С	Skillful
	Flutter	Experienced	iOS Development	Skillful
	Git	Experienced	Data Science	Skillful
	JavaScript	Experienced	Android Development	Skillful
	HTML/CSS	Experienced	PHP	Skillful
	Java	Skillful	SQL	Skillful
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Mar 2021 — Present	Founder, Alpha Ventu	ires		Orlando
	Achieved a trust score 300% over 90 days	e of 96% as Head of Investmips with over 20 Web 3.0 cor	nent Analysis, which resulted in a me	

Researcher, Center for Microgravity Research at The University of Central Florida

Jan 2017 — Jan 2018

• Researched and performed physical experiments in a microgravity environment on behalf of the University of Central Florida

Orlando